//Questions.js
// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Bibble',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 16,
  perQuestionScore: 1,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'How many years ago was the bible written?',
      choices: ['1400', '1000', '1600', 'None of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '1600',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many sections are there in a bible?',
      choices: ['One', 'Four', 'Six', 'Two'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Two',
    },
    {
      question:
        'How many authors wrote the bible?',
      choices: ['40', '35', '20', 'All of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '40',
    },
    {
      question: 'In which language was the bible originally written?',
      choices: ['Hebrew', 'Aramaic', 'Greek', 'All of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'All the above',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many book in bible?',
      choices: ['78', '66', '46', 'None of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '66',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many book in Old Testament?',
      choices: ['39', '29', '38', '27'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '39',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many book in New Testament?',
      choices: ['27', '39', '22', '29'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '27',
    },
	{
      question: 'In which language was the Old Testament originally written?',
      choices: ['Hebrew and Aramaic', 'Aramaic', 'Greek', 'Hebrew'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Hebrew and Aramaic',
    },
	{
      question: 'In which language was the New Testament originally written ?',
      choices: ['Hebrew', 'Aramaic', 'Greek', 'Latin'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Greek',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many verses in the bible?',
      choices: ['20333', '50234', '10456', '31103'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '31103',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many words in the bible ?',
      choices: ['903456', '807361', '102892', 'None of the above'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '807361',
    },
	{
      question: 'Which Chapter is the Shortest in the bible?',
      choices: ['Psalm 117', 'Juda', 'Psalm 23', 'Psalm 117 and Psalm 23'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Psalm 117',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many Chapter in the bible?',
      choices: ['2189', '1189', '1000', '2000'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '1189',
    },
	{
      question: 'Which Chapter is the longest in the bible?',
      choices: ['John', 'Genesis', 'Psalm 119', 'Revelation'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Psalm 119',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many Chapter in Old Testament?',
      choices: ['900', '1000', '590', '929'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '929',
    },
	{
      question: 'How many chapter in New Testament?',
      choices: ['929', '129', '260', '189'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '260',
    },
	
  ],
}